One dream, one wish.
If you want it, gotta go over the top.
Setting sail and heading for the unknown.
Cutting through the
winds and waves as I go.
Gotta keep it up, never stopping, no!
Cause I'm aiming to get there first, yeah.
It's all or nothing, no time to worry.
Do it later, right now I'm living free.
When your foes look like
they will overwhelm you?
It means your heart's saying
this is what you can't do.
Despite all that to run is not an option.
Once they're closed, they
feel the satisfaction.
You think I'm rude,
here's my appreciation.
When things are getting
tough, just gotta smile.
If you are going on your way?
And you're looking for
a fresh, brand new day?
Then make sure your only
thought you have is Yes, I can!
As you're on your way?
Marked maps will be made.
Yes, with every step that you will take.
Just look at all you've been through.
Look ahead at new horizons.
In view shining brightly.
Oh, who knows what's waiting for you?
Dream living, that's the way.
Make like a hurricane.
Now, got to make your mark today.
One dream, one wish.
Your dreams don't run away.
Go for the knockout.
You doubted the loyalty of my crew.
I won't forget it.
At times like these, we
have to focus on the battle!
and trust each other completely?
or we'll die out there.
I get why he was mad, but
he didn't have to ditch us.
Hope he comes back.
Frickin' Shinobu!
She really screwed this one up for us!
You can't really blame her
for acting that way, though.
Kaido came in, took over her country,
trashed it, and screwed up
her life in the process.
She's been waiting 20 long years
for this plan to come together.
I getcha.
But even if Law's crew did rent us
out, I couldn't blame them either.
Yeah?
Because that's what you would do?
Oh, please.
You'd squeal in one minute.
Uh, if I was being tortured,
more like three seconds.
That's too short even
for me! Piss off! Huh?
I don't need help from lower-class scum!
What the heck?
Since when does anyone get
angry in Ebisu town anyway?
I see.
This must be that hag
monster's curse! God!
They must be the new fellas.
They arrived from the capital.
I heard they were kicked out yesterday.
What are you looking at?
You little squirts better get lost.
They were forced out?
Yes.
Only those who are loyal to the Shogun and
can make profits are
permitted to live there.
But from what I heard?
Those men were up to some bad business.
and earned their banishment.
See him?
That's Bongo the underling.
That one was into some
real naughty business.
He went around setting fires at night, but
paid off officials to avoid punishment.
An arsonist?
He paid bribes just to torment people?
It was more than just a hobby.
He was in cahoots with someone else,
namely a lumber dealer who sold supplies?
for rebuilding burned houses.
That's bongo.
Huh?
That's not all, I'm afraid.
A third man, a priest and undertaker,
exploited the fire victims.
In their time of mourning, he
gouged them on funeral costs.
That's bingo.
That's awful.
They were working together? Yes.
Bingo Bongo and Bungo are our bad bunch.
A band of bamboozlers.
Scumbags.
Who does that?
Alas, because they paid off the
officials, they weren't arrested.
They got away with everything without
so much as a slap on the wrist.
On the outside, they
looked like decent men,
but on the inside, they
were rotten to the core.
Here's the kicker.
All three of them were head over heels
in love with the beautiful Gomorrah Saki.
She's the Oiran who met an
untimely death just yesterday.
Apparently, they all went
bankrupt trying to woo her,
throwing all the money
they owned at her feet.
So I suppose they got their
just desserts in the end.
Thank the gods.
At least the story ends well.
I don't know.
Those rumors seem really specific.
But I'm sure they must hold some weight.
And the way you tell it, I bet that
Oiran tricked them on purpose. Nice.
I can't help but wonder
what she was really like.
Wait, I know them! Hmm?
I saw them before!
They threw a fit!
They were making a big scene
at the Oideron's procession!
Yasuie, bless his soul, was helping them
pick out a house and showing them around.
Not that those ungrateful
miscreants appreciated it.
Wow, seriously?
What a guy!
He really is nice to everyone, huh?
I bet you recruited a slew of
new people, so not always lost!
Would you please pass on a
message to my pal, Kinamon?
Tell him that once the fight starts,
he'll have us at his side, no matter what.
He is your pal, is he?
It's been a pleasure
seeing the both of you.
Now, if you'll excuse
me, we've got lots to do.
Hey, don't leave yet.
There's no time to lose.
Plenty of folks are likely
to die in the next week.
Let's go!
We have our work cut out
for us and then some.
Alrighty, I'll see you later.
Looking sharp, handsome!
You two beautiful...
Good afternoon, young lady.
You three have a wonderful
day now. Take care!
Well, that was weird. What's his deal?
He was running his mouth
like you were good friends,
but I couldn't figure out
how you were connected.
I couldn't tell either.
Yes, I thought he was rather charming.
Are the three of you close?
Who is he?
The truth is...
We haven't a clue.
Wait, you don't know who he is?
Why'd you talk to him the
whole time without asking?
He just drolled on and on.
I couldn't get word in.
How do you forget someone
like that, though?
The fact that he spoke to us
with such familiarity puzzled me.
Besides that, what if he
indeed was a man of importance?
Alas, I'd look a fool!
Was he a childhood friend of yours?
Or perhaps a mentor?
He seemed so comfortable
and happy in your presence.
Just tell me already!
How would we know?
I've had enough.
Kill him!
Make him pay!
Hang on tight, okay?
I believe I know what
you mean by Haki now.
It's called Riyuo in the land of Wano.
Riyuo, huh?
The term means flow.
When you're using Haki, you let it
run through your body, don't you?
You must feel it first.
Right!
I just gotta let it flow!
You need to pull back!
I touched him!
Messed it up!
You're over-stressing yourself.
Allow the Haki to move to your fist
from the parts that don't use it.
Your time's up, Straw Hat!
See ya clear!
Still off!
It doesn't work!
What's the trick?
Nope! No! Dammit!
How do you do it?
I'm getting sick of this!
My Haki won't flow the right way!
He just keeps on taking them down.
Can't kill stupid.
Damn!
Focus your Haki.
It won't flow into an angry fist.
Who's gonna step up next?
Let's go now!
How do you do, Pops?
How are those old stomach
cramps treating you?
Oh, hello, Yasuie.
It's not a lot, but I'm leaving
some millet and water for you.
So make sure to eat up.
You're a helpful fellow,
Yasuie. Thank you.
Oh, why, it was nothing, nothing at all.
But I'm delighted to help out.
Really.
Here.
I'll even throw in another bag for you.
See you, pups. Daddy.
Yoo-hoo.
Do you have enough medicine,
seaweed shop, sweetie?
I'm afraid not.
But truth be told, seeing
you always cheers me up.
Ah!
You talk to everyone that way?
Oh, hey, mister.
How's the knee holding up? Yes, Sue.
You want to play?
Hey, you Huang.
Is your mama feeling better?
Oh, Saki, how's the baby doing?
Oh!
Over here!
Don't forget to say hi to us, too.
Here, everybody.
It's not much, but take these.
Thank you, as always.
Wow, he's so generous.
Is he rich? Nice guy.
Spreading his wealth around town.
Quite the contrary.
The poor man works himself to
the bone and gets paid peanuts.
He has a daughter, a girl named Dock, but
she was sold into a job at the capital.
She sends most of her
earnings back here to Yasuie.
We don't say.
Dock, that's me!
Oh, it's her.
Since so much of his
money is sent from Dock,
he says it isn't right
to keep it for himself.
So he goes around and spreads
it to those less fortunate.
A blessing for those
of us too weak to work.
He may come across as foolish, but
he's a beloved member of our community?
who supported us for so long.
He's our saint.
I miss you, Daddy.
Daddy!
We're done for today. Go to sleep!
It's not fair.
I've got plenty of fight left.
Why do we gotta wait till tomorrow?
I'm hungry.
Aren't you guys going to at least feed us?
Stop yapping like a dog.
Shut up and sleep.
I'm going to turn into
a mummy by tomorrow.
May I ask you something, Mr. Straw Hat?
Go ahead.
Why are you so eager to fight Kaido?
I heard you lost to him in Kuri.
I can't talk yet.
There, that'll work.
Now I'll say it.
Hmm?
You know the Four Emperors?
I don't.
They're called that because they're
the most powerful pirates out there,
supposedly unbeatable.
Well, one of those guys is Kaido.
I'm going to be king of the pirates,
so that means I've got to
take them all down to do it.
The pirate king?
You want to become a gold roger?
Wait, are you saying you
know about him, old man?
Yes, he visited the land of
Wano quite some time ago.
Huh.
That lines up with what Keenumont said.
Huh?
What did you say?
Are you telling me you know him?
Is my hearing off?
What is that crap?
It can't be! Rizal?
Greetings, Straw Hat.
What the hell?
I don't know.
I don't think this is
the real Raizo. It is.
Why are you inside that guy?
You're still alive, Raizo? How?
I shall explain all to you, Sir Hyogoro.
That's him!
It's Uchimichu Koza!
You're cornered now!
Grab him!
I can't believe it's really you.
It is indeed.
And I assure you, I am as surprised
by our meeting as you are.
Oh. Unbelievable.
So tell me,
does this mean that your
desperate plan was successful
and you really arrived here
for 20 years in the past?
Yes, indeed.
Thanks to Lady Toki's sorcery. Hmm.
That's incredible.
What I don't get is why
you're here, caribou.
Go away!
Hey, don't be like that, Straw Hat.
We're pals, aren't we?
What gives here, Rhizo?
I thought you only came
here to break me out.
Why are you helping this Garp? Aw.
No need to be such a Moon.
I might come in handy after all.
I'm your underling.
Give me orders, chief.
Well, in exchange for just one thing,
may I have a ride home
on your ship with you?
Tough luck, pal.
You're stranded here.
But I've realized the error of my ways.
Don't you see?
I'm a changed man, I swear!
Please, sir!
Okay, it's a deal, but
only because you changed.
Wow, really?
Thank you!
Is this some kind of trap?
That was way too easy.
Sir Luffy Taro, the groveling fellow
has quite a remarkable skill set.
He shall be of great service to us.
For so long, I thought my fate
was sealed, but I didn't give up,
I kept clinging on to this
wretched life, I'm so glad!
Huh?
Are you all right, sir?
How close I came to letting
myself die in this prison,
I had accepted death!
If this had happened a moment too late, I
might have died, never knowing the truth?
So the Akazaya Samurai
are still alive, are they?
And that isn't all?
Odin's son Kozuki Momonosuke too?
It's more than some tall tale.
The rebel's flame still burns bright.
Rise off! And Mr. Straw Hat!
I may be old, but for my country's sake,
I will always have fight left in me.
May I join you?
There must be something I can do.
It would be an honor to have you.
Sir Luffy,
this man kneeling before you was once the
greatest Yakuza boss in the land of Lardo!
Yeah?
So you were a big deal
back in the day, old man?
You mentioned that you've been gathering
supporters for the cause
in the Flower Capital.
Is that right?
Indeed!
Then it really must be fate that
brought you here to Udon, hmm?
Located in this labor camp, there
are four other excavation sites?
just as vast as this one.
Not to mention tens of thousands
of prisoners exactly like us.
However, the inmates here were
locked up for petty theft or assault.
Nearly every single one of
them are guilty of rebellion.
Against Shogun orgy?
Of course!
Why did this not occur to me?
The rage of this country is
ready to burst from these gates.
The Yakuza leaders who once supported Wano
from the shadows are
all held at this prison.
I will converse with them.
I'm certain that they'll
join the cause for Kozuki.
Raizo, see that cell there?
Yes, I am aware.
I have exchanged words with Kawamatsu.
He is the first one that I shall set free.
Perfect, then.
All I gotta do is rip this place apart.
Then we'll get a whole
crap load of new friends!
Sir Luffy, are you mad?
Lower your voice! Right!
Sounds like a plan to me!
Now, give me some drugs!
This is it.
I'm gonna die.
I'm hungry, I'm tired, and
there's no horse here to call.
Farewell, Okiku.
Our sharkodile is exhausted too, but I'm
happy to say we have already entered Udon.
I'm coming for you, my sweet, sweet love.
This might get messy.
It's so good!
I want more!
Wait for me, dear suit.
Breaking news!
He's locked up!
Ushimitsu Koza, the elusive thief
terrorizing the flower capital, was caught!
Read about it!
Take a flyer!
Lord Orochi, apologies for the intrusion.
If I could have a moment of your time.
It's concerning that troublesome thief.
We have apprehended him.
Silence, you fool!
I am in mourning for the love of my life!
You will never understand the pain
of losing such a beautiful woman!
You do have my sympathy, Shogun.
I recognize you're experiencing
grief, but with all due respect, sir.
Kiyoshiro had to take appropriate actions.
If we allowed her transgressions
to pass, you would have lost face.
This situation would have undermined
your authority and reputation.
Lord Orochi, I don't care about
some miserable little robber.
That's trivial to me.
There is no woman alive
who could ever compete
with her immense beauty
and I was robbed of her.
Can't you see I want to be left to myself?
Despite your sorrow, it's nice you
have emerged from your quarters.
But I must strongly
insist you listen to me.
The matter is pressing.
Ushimitsu Koza was not
your typical petty thief.
On the surface, he's a crook with a hero
complex, bent on helping the lower class.
A menace to the rich!
He's run amok on the flower
capital for quite some time now,
but something greater is at play.
As previously mentioned,
he's currently being held at the
prisoner's quarters in Rasetsu Town.
But his identity is the interesting part.
What?
It can't be!
How is the bastard still alive?
After all this time Is this a joke?
Right under my nose, no less
Course me clan, huh?
Why didn't you tell me this?
Anyone but him?
And why now?
Lord Orochi, sir, we await your order.
What would you have us do with him?
Do you really need to ask?
The man must die!
Make an example of him
with a public execution!
Put it on lightstraws everywhere!
Make certain that all can see!
It's already taken care of.
Don't you worry.
Kyoshiro!
As you know, today is the day that
Komorosaki's public funeral will be held.
With so many people in attendance,
we expect that the event
might become a bit unruly.
I took it upon myself to prepare.
Yes, yes! Splendid!
What is your order, sir?
all right i have an idea yes
have him personally accompany
kumasaki to the grave that wretched
little bastard will die today
it's a two-for-one funeral some
of the brightest stars of the city
buried together what a wicked twist
of fate excellent thinking my lord now
bring me my ride i intend to witness
the entire tragedy go down that's not
funny you're in the booze early again
aren't you kaido stop joking around
sorry it's true it's no
fair it can't be go check
your freaking light scroll
if you don't believe me.
It killed me!
Ah!
Komurasaki!
It's over.
We couldn't hide it.
He knows about the Oiran's death.
This is going to suck.
Expect him to be moody for weeks.
That's no good.
Can we do something?
Hey!
Come on, Balloon!
Dude, why is taking so long?
Shut up!
There's been a change of plans now.
Huh?
Not if I say so!
Let's get going already!
We don't have all day!
Oh?
What the hell happened to you
two between last night and today?
This is what I'm always like.
What you talking about?
Oh, are you sure?
Hey, you think it's a bad time to
tell him all his soup went missing?
Overnight too are you dumb who knows what
he'll do if he's hit with
more bad news i agree?
Kind of wondering how that much food
just uh walked away you did hear
me yes i advised Sir Luffy not to
gorge himself devouring the entire
pot was irresponsible of him given
his Circumstance how does this
idiot keep surviving what is his
secret let's start the sumo match!
I ain't got time to deal
with your nonsense today.
I have something to tend to. Hey, you.
Show me the flower capital right now.
Get the light scroll snail.
It's prepared.
Ready for signal.
Let's see what's going on over there.
A video transponder snail.
Oh, no.
Oh, I see.
That must be the flower capital.
They dared to steal our food and weapons.
Show the Otamayama Thieves Brigade
what happens to those who cross us.
I'm tired of going in circles.
I'll shut your lying mouth with
my trick mechanism so hard!
Won't be long before the Atamayama
Thieves Brigade collapses.
The fire's spreading too fast!
We can't put it out. It's massive.
Damn, Hold 'em screwed us over!
They're turned to Bekori Town!
Are you sure, sir?
Will Kaido's men come
after us if we go there?
What makes you think I care?
So what?
I'll kick all their asses!
That's a shame.
In that case, Ashura Doji
has my deepest sympathy.
Indeed.
And yet this was for the greater good.
Despite its dire cost let's travel
to Bakada town I know not what
direction to take Now that our
initial plans have been thwarted we
shall focus on one task ensuring
that Ashita goes to battle with our
enemy Otherwise I fear our struggle
may be lost before it even begins
I'm back
Excuse me, who the heck is that?
What in the world is going on here?
Oh, hey, Brooke What's up with you?
Why are you here?
Oh, Zoro If I had ice, they would be
bugging out at the sight I'm seeing.
Although I suppose I could
literally drop my jaw to the floor.
Apologies for the intrusion.
I'll see myself out now.
Wait, hey, it's not what it looks like.
Get back here. Huh?
Don't mind if I do.
My mistake, then.
Whoa.
What beauty.
Pardon me for being so bold, but may
I have a look at your panties, please?
Huh?
It's fine he's a friend
Prepare for me a fine feast
or else I shall curse you!
I'm scared
Kin'emon instructed me to
stay here and scare off
people with that whole
haunted house bed I see.
How funny.
I wondered why so many people
left offerings outside.
Wow, it's incredible to think that you
were the younger sister of Momonosuke.
Beautiful like the Oiran,
a sight for sore eyes.
If I had a bear!
Because she is an Oiran, silly!
How did you settle down
with someone like her?
I'm quite envious, Oro.
We were only sleeping, you dumbass.
Please tell him. Apologies.
It was freezing and body heat
is a good source of warmth.
However, you're lucky.
Men are usually besotted by the
thought of sleeping next to me.
You should be thankful.
So be honest, you loved it, right?
Damn, you are pretty forward, lady. Yes.
Anyway, I hope that the rest of
our crew isn't too far behind us.
The women set out to use
the bathhouse yesterday,
but when I tried to find them, it
was no use, as you might guess.
Also, the flower capital is in a
state of chaos, if you didn't know.
People are pouring into
the city by the masses.
It's the funeral of Wano's
most beautiful woman, you see.
And they captured some thief who
steals money and gives to the poor.
Ushimitsu Koza is his name, and
he seems as if he was a big deal.
Where did you hear that news?
It can't be. No, it's all true. Here.
Read about it in this flyer.
He'll be executed in the capital today.
His real identity has been
a mystery until recently.
Sounds like he was quite
beloved in Ebisu Town.
Did you say Ebisu Town? Oh, yeah.
And there's more written.
If I remember, he goes by the
name something Yasuie, I think.
Chono Yasuie?
That's the name?
How'd you know?
Chaka.
Hey, what's with her?
Come back, Chaka!
Thank you for saving our lives yesterday.
We shall never forget your kindness.
Don't be stupid!
You couldn't even protect her by yourself!
I'm going!
Where are you guys all running to?
I just got here!
Wait up! Everyone! Hey!
Get up.
Time to go.
Greetings.
You come to escort me.
That is mighty kind of you fellows.
What?
It can't be.
He was caught?
Where do you think you're going, kid?
There's people who want you
dead out there, remember?
Stop it! Let go!
He needs my help! Calm down!
We've got to get a grip!
Let me go!
What has gotten into her? Taco!
They're going to kill him!
Please let me go!
I have to help him somehow!
My daddy will die if I don't go!
Taco...
What the hell did you say?
What fine weather today.
Such a pleasant time to
be in the flower capital.